[
  {
    "question": "How many countries in the world have square flags?",
    "answer": "Switzerland and Vatican City",
    "tags": "fun-with-flags",
    "date": "2022-09-09"
  },
  {
    "question": "There are only 3 countries in the world that have a dragon in their flag. Name one.",
    "answer": "Bhutan, Wales, Malta",
    "tags": "fun-with-flags",
    "date": "2022-09-09"
  },
  {
    "question": "Only two countries have their map on their flag. Name one.",
    "answer": "Kosovo and Cyprus",
    "tags": "fun-with-flags",
    "date": "2022-09-09"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which National Flags display a Lion?",
    "answer": "Bermuda, Jersey, Spain, Sri Lanka, and Luxembourg",
    "tags": "fun-with-flags",
    "date": "2022-09-09"
  },
  {
    "question": "It is normally a criminal offence to mutilate or burn the national flag. There’s only one reason why you can burn the US flag. Which is?",
    "answer": "It can’t be fixed or is dirty upon cleaning",
    "tags": "fun-with-flags",
    "date": "2022-09-09"
  },
  {
    "question": "The flag of Paraguay has the unique feature of what?",
    "answer": "",
    "tags": "fun-with-flags",
    "date": "2022-09-09"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is the most common color on national flags?",
    "answer": "Red, 105 flags. Red symbolizes bravery and sufferance, blue Sky-Ocean but also Peace and freedom, Black: self-determinism ethnic heritage",
    "tags": "fun-with-flags",
    "date": "2022-09-09"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many colors are there in the South African Flag?",
    "answer": "Six: Black, Yellow, Green, White, Black, Red, Blue",
    "tags": "fun-with-flags",
    "date": "2022-09-09"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which country has the oldest flag?",
    "answer": "first used in 1925, the design goes back to 1219",
    "tags": "fun-with-flags",
    "date": "2022-09-09"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is the only flag in the world that doesn’t have 4 edges?",
    "answer": "Nepal",
    "tags": "fun-with-flags",
    "date": "2022-09-09"
  }
]
